We need to get them!
Follow them! Catch them!
Get away!
This is Ranma of the Saotome
School of Anything Goes Martial Arts.
And this is Akane of the Tendo Dojo.
These two teens were arranged
to be married by their parents.
- Huh?
My fate is my own!
What a nuisance you are!
Unfortunately Ranma has
a bit of a problem.
When splashed with cold water,
he transforms into a girl.
What the hell was that for?
Get back here!
RANMA1/2
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you so much for your patience...
...I'd apologize
but we know that's the way it is.
A scorching flower blooms feverishly
amid the freezing winds of the ice rink,
caught between red-hot passion
and chilly composure.
Flying, turning, gliding,
slipping, sliding,
the bloom is the one and only
Daydream Flower,
better known to pop-song lovers
as musobana.
These young skaters are competing
to the bitter end
to try and grasp that dream of victory,
the Charlotte Cup!
Through heaven and earth,
I alone will dare to forge
toward an unparalleled event
for the first, and possibly last, time.
Unheard, unsung, un-ionized,
my two cents make no sense at all.
I pity the fool that doesn't realize
the balcony is closed,
but knowing is half the battle.
When I've fallen and I can't get up,
na-noo, na-noo.
Do tears of glory await them at the end
of these trials and tribulations?
Who will brush aside
the Goddess of Victory's glorious bangs
like a modern-day Alexander Nevsky?
I don't want you to take your eyes
off this match for a single moment.
Even a glance away
could cost you precious details!
Well, I've kept the audience waiting
long enough.
The final arc of this
Martial Skating maelstrom begins!
It's time to witness the clash
of two great rivals!
And now,
our unprecedented match continues.
It's the Martial Skating showdown
between Kolkhoz High School
and Furinkan High School.
The ice cracks that remain in the rink
look like Antarctica.
With a fresh new pair switched in
to represent Furinkan High School,
the match begins with a new fire.
Ranma, Ryoga, do your best out there.
Bring it on, Sanzenin.
Prepare yourself!
Come on, Charlotte.
You need to give up and accept that
the two of us are going home together.
You, with the pigtail. To me.
Fall right into my arms.
Yeah. Just try
and catch this flight if you can!
Crap, I forgot I was as banged up as I am.
Now, what's gotten you so upset?
I would have thought
you'd be happy to receive a kiss from me.
I don't want a kiss from a weirdo!
I don't give a crap who you think you are.
Try anything again and you're dead!
I see. If that's how you feel...
Mmm?
You must be feeling jealous
of Akane Tendo.
Huh?
It'll be okay. No need to worry.
My special skill allows me to love
every woman in equal measure.
And my dear, my love for you is
deeper than the ocean.
Oh, cute!
No way!
I cannot begin to overstate
how deluded you are.
Don't you get it?
How many times do I have to tell you
I'm not Charlotte?
Oh? You're not? Well do you have any idea
where Charlotte might be?
- I l-let it go back in the wild.
- Huh?
I felt sorry that it was being forced
to go along with this.
It gave me this collar as a parting gift
before it left.
So please, just give this up.
Whoa.
You gotta give me some warning!
Hmm?
Oh, no. Did I make you cry?
- Give it back now.
- Huh?
Give me back my Charlotte!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Give it back! Give it back! Give it back!
Give it back!
How is she that strong?
Hey, what the hell are you doing?
Shut your mouth!
You're one to talk, when you're sporting
a huge lump on the back of your head.
- Hmm?
- The nerve.
Ow!
Whatever. We still need
to come up with a plan.
A plan?
I don't want to,
but we gotta work together.
Ugh! No, we don't.
We might be paired up
but I'm not going to work with you.
You just got
your ass handed to you!
Look, I'm pretty beat-up too.
We have to prioritize winning
right now.
Listen to me, Ryoga.
Fine. Out with it.
Oh, hang on. What could be going on now?
The pair from Furinkan High School
seems to be deep in conversation.
So is it possible we're about to witness
a change in the duo's plan of attack?
What? How could you say that?
You're just a big bully.
So, what? Am I not good enough
for you anymore?
- Are you serious?
- You're a bully.
Nothing but a pig-headed low-down
insensitive bully.
Where do you get off
saying that to me?
What is this?
Why are you always so violent?
You awful, feral shrew!
You and I are done. Good day!
Why is it
I so often find myself alone?
I guess he's the only one
who truly loves me.
At long last she understands.
My pigtailed beauty.
Here I come, to cradle you in consolation.
Darling. You're not hurt, are you?
It's really you, my beloved!
- Just kidding!
- Whoa!
Tricky minx.
Thanks for the help.
No! San-chan!
Time to pay you back for earlier.
So prepare yourself.
I'm just a little baby.
Could you two live with yourselves
if you bullied me?
You're just a couple of cowards.
Yeah, she does have a point.
Ah, that was close.
I didn't think you would play that dirty.
- Scary!
- Whoa!
You may be a girl,
but a match is a match! Sorry.
Ow.
It hurts!
Oh, incredible!
A remarkable showcase of teamwork
from Furinkan High!
Oh, wow! Well done, you two!
Akane went out of her way
to congratulate me.
The two of us, you mean.
No, me.
Both of us.
To me.
It's too early for you guys to celebrate.
When did they get up?
Well if that's how you wanted to play
this, we'll have to bring our A-game.
Can't admit when you're beat.
Just watch what I can do, Akane.
- Here I go--
- Hold it right there.
What are you doing?
You're not winning this thing on your own.
You two need to pay attention!
Huh?
Doth mine eyes deceive me?
Are they curling?
Oh! An amazing double whammy!
Seriously, what is going on here?
It's all your fault!
You shouldn't have gotten in my way.
Ah, shut up already.
- What?
- You're only trying to show off for Akane.
Stop messing this up for me.
This is why
you're never gonna be able to beat me.
You're never gonna be able to beat me.
Never gonna be able to beat me.
Are you even listening?
Uh, hello?
Very well. Let's take a moment
to finally settle this here and now.
Huh?
Whoa!
Pay attention!
I know which of us is better for her.
And it's me!
Ha! You fell for it! Now's my chance!
Ah! He's gone and locked into
a German suplex!
This is intense!
That could've been bad.
Give me back my Charlotte!
Hmm?
I'm ending this!
Huh?
Ha!
Akane, please, give me strength!
Whoa!
I won.
Wow! You are amazing!
Is this really the end
for Mikado Sanzenin?
Has Kolkhoz High School been knocked out?
San-chan.
This blanket is so cute!
Don't you take my blanket, you wench!
- Hey, just let it go!
- I should be saying the same thing!
You shouldn't be hogging Martine!
I love you, Martine.
Hmm, yeah, he's been knocked out.
The winner, Furinkan High School!
Knockout! Kolkhoz's golden pair
accept the bitter taste of defeat.
The victory goes to Furinkan High School!
I won for you, Akane.
This isn't over yet,
you hear me?
You never know when to give up,
do you, Ranma?
I must admit, I admire your tenacity,
but Akane is mine to claim!
You get that she's not a cat, right?
It's not like I can
just hand her over to you.
Hyah!
Now knock it off!
And get your head
back in the game, you idiot.
I can't just leave Akane alone.
Not with a half-assed jerk like you.
It's still better than being with a pig!
I'm done playing the nice guy!
You can go to hell, nice guy!
Ugh! Both of you need to cut it out!
- Wh...
- What the hell was that for, Akane?
Why is it that you two are
always at each other's throats?
Oh, shut up! You should keep your nose
out of this!
So there is something then.
You have to tell me what's going on.
Why do the two of you keep picking
at each other?
Because I have to beat Ryoga--
We can sit down and have
a long conversation about this later.
Get off me!
What do you even have to talk about?
- I don't wanna hear it from you.
- Hey, come on!
Quit squealing, you nasty pig!
I'll end you if I have to!
- What's that?
- I already told you to stop!
Now's my chance!
No. Akane!
Geez. That's why I said to butt out.
Oh, no.
She doesn't know how to swim?
- Akane!
Huh? Dude.
What do you want?
You good?
Akane!
Huh?
Oh! Good, you're awake.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I, uh...
Huh?
Ranma?
Heads up.
What happened?
And why is P-chan all wet too?
Brave boy. He bit you and dragged you
over to safety.
We have no idea how he could've jumped in.
I see.
Thank you so much, P-chan.
You should thank Ryoga too.
He was the first person
to try and jump in to save you.
Oh, yeah, where did he run off to?
He hasn't gotten back yet?
Well, in light of all
the stupid crap you kept pulling today,
why don't we just call it a draw?
Oh?
Huh?
Shampoo!
Ranma, you're dead.
Shampoo.
I'll kill you!
Um, what's going on?
It's all right.
I thought I was done with you.
Go away already!
- Ranma?
- Went that way.
Ugh! Damn it!
Whoa. Who the heck was that girl?
So what's the story
with you and that girl?
Uh, a long one.
She sure was pretty though, wasn't she?
For real? Remember she's trying
to kill me, you idiot!
- Yeah?
- Listen to me!
Yeah?
I'll never forget it.
It was a few months ago.
So hungry.
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
This is the Chinese Amazon village.
Chinese Amazons? What are they again?
All of the women that come from
this village are incredibly strong.
Oh.
Oh, sounds like they're having
a contest today.
Winning this martial arts contest is
quite the accomplishment.
- Wow.
- I would say
that one girl's pretty strong.
FIRST PRIZE
So, uh, what do you two think
you're eating?
Mmm? A meat bun?
Hmm?
She was saying, "What the hell?
Why does that girl and her panda believe
they can start helping themselves
to my prize?"
Your prize?
She said, "It's the annual
martial arts contest,
and I just won the fight
that declared me its champion."
Well, if I beat you
then I guess you can't complain, right?
Hmm.
Aiyaa...
Wow! She won immediately!
What's up?
Aiyaa!
Whoa!
I thought you said you were both girls
when this happened.
Let me finish.
Oh!
Hmm.
We have to run away! Now!
Huh? But why?
You've just become a recipient
of the Kiss of Death!
What the heck is a Kiss of Death?
The Chinese Amazons are
a very proud people.
Losing to an outsider
is a dishonor worse than death.
The Kiss of Death is a solemn vow,
one that requires her
to chase you down to the depths of hell
in pursuit of killing you.
So that's
why she started following me.
It didn't matter where I went in China,
she was never far behind.
Now she's followed you
all the way to Japan.
Pretty impressive, huh, P-chan?
Well, it must be nice that
your assassin is a pretty, young girl.
Really not wanting
that kind of consolation.
I'm back.
Hello, Ranma.
Someone's here to visit you.
Oh, yeah? I wonder who it is.
Mr. Saotome brought her in with him.
Wha... Why?
You freak-ass.
What were you thinking, you crazy old man?
SHE FOLLOWED ME
Ranma?
- Hmm.
- Hello.
- Yeah. Uh.
You're a man?
Yeah, and, uh,
it's a real shame I'm not a girl.
Oh! So this must be the first time
she's gotten to see you as a boy?
Ryoga, you're back.
How surprisingly perceptive
for you to notice, P-chan.
Wha... You think you have the right
to talk to me like that, huh?
Come on, man.
What crap are you trying to pull here?
This nice lady came
all the way from China.
Now be a girl for her.
Give me Ranma.
I don't know where she is!
Ranma. She's here.
You hide her. I kill you!
Leave her alone.
Argh. Don't get in my way!
Don't come in someone's house
to pick a fight!
Well, that's no good.
Poor girl.
I guess this means she ended up losing
a second time.
Uh, it was an accident!
I didn't do anything!
There's no need for you to be so modest
about this, is there? You won the match.
KNOCKOUT!!
Well, yeah, but that was just...
So does this mean she's gonna be setting
her crosshairs on male Ranma too?
Oh, no!
This was all an accident
and you did not lose!
Liar!
Now accept your Kiss of Death
with some dignity.
Hmm.
Mmm? What?
Wha...
KISS OF DEATH